https://safetyconcepts.co.uk/privacy-notice/

Privacy noticeThis privacy notice applies to the services we provide our customers in the pursuit of our business. It applies to all personal data we may collect and retain, including names, email addresses and telephone numbers.It applies if you’re not currently our customer but you interact with us via our website or call us by telephone.This notice does not apply to other organisations whom you may contact via links on our website, or through our recommendation.This notice will be reviewed regularly and updates made where required.Safety Concepts Ltd places great importance on personal data protection. We will only collect and retain personal information which is current and relevant to our needs.We collect information about you when you call us, email us or interact with us via our website. The personal information we collect and retain is generally limited to your name and contact details. We do not usually need any other personal information about you in order to provide our services.Circumstances may arise when other personal data comes into our possession, for example in the case of an accident or incident investigation. Under these circumstances, personal data will be held securely, not shared, and retained until there is no legal need to retain it further, at which time it will be destroyed.We process all personal data on the legal basis of “legitimate interests” under the General Data Protection Regulation: this means that without the personal data that we process, we are unable to serve you, our customer.We will never share your data with any third party. If the need should arise to share your information we will seek your explicit consent before we do so, unless required by law to disclose information.You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us. If you think that your personal information may be inaccurate or out of date, please let us know and we will correct or remove information where appropriate.CookiesWe use cookies on our website which anonymously remember your computer or device and keep track of browsing patterns so we can build up a picture of how our website is being used. No data which can be used to identify you is stored in this way.Other cookies remember your registration and login details to make your next visit easier. You may turn off cookies in your browser settings.Contact UsAbout usWe are a leading Safety and Environmental and ISO consultancy. Since 1999 we have provided compliance, tender-winning support, and cost savings for 300 UK companies.Privacy noticeMore infoHomeAbout usServicesIndustriesSmall businessesTrainingInsightsContactContact details51 High Street, Arundel, BN18 9AJ01903 885297contact@safetyconcepts.co.ukRecent Posts
Coronavirus: what should I do?
GDPR: has the world gone mad?
HSE 2017 statistics show rise in work-related mental health absences
HSE 2017
HSE strategy: Helping Great Britain Work Well
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use the site we will assume that that's OK with you.OkRead more
